Finding Aid for the Peter H. Prince Papers MS.2921
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Research Files, 1770-2006; I
  - Sevier County, Tennessee, 1861-2005; C
    - Elkmont: W. E. Ijams, 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Elkmont: CCC Camp 1212 (est. 1933 October 20), undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Elkmont: Elkmont Grill (opened 2004 November 20), 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Elkmont: Little River Lumber Co., 1927-1985 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Elkmont: Airplane Crash (1928), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Elkmont: Elkmont, 1925-1999; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 58, Folder 7] (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Elkmont: Wonderland Hotel, 1983; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 58, Folder 8] (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Elkmont: Elkmont Cottages, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Elkmont: Elkmont, 1996-2003; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 58, Folder 9] (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Elkmont: Little River Railroad, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Elkmont: Little River Floods, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Elkmont: Little River Road, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Elkmont: The Appalachian Club, 1929-1999 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Elkmont: Little River Lumber Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Elkmont: Camp LeConte, 1933-1937 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Elkmont: Elkmont School, 1922-1986 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Elkmont: Elkmont Baptist Church, 1985-1992 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Elkmont: Elkmont Hotel, circa 1920 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Elkmont: Champion Fibre Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Elkmont: Little River Road, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Elkmont: Levi Trentham Grist Mill, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Elkmont: Clementine Tine Metcalf Mill, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Blanket Mountain: Blanket Mountain (4609'), 1904-1925 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Blanket Mountain: Fish Camp, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Blanket Mountain: Fish Camp School, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Blanket Mountain: Jake's Creek Logging Camp, 1925-1987 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Blanket Mountain: Cucumber Gap, 1984-1991 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Blanket Mountain: Higdon Camp, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Blanket Mountain: Camp No. 2, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Blanket Mountain: Rough Fork Flume Town, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Blanket Mountain: Ming Ridge CCC Camp 1212, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Blanket Mountain: Camp 8, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Blanket Mountain: Mids Branch and Mids Gap, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Blanket Mountain: Camp 3, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Blanket Mountain: Big Medicine Lumber Camp, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Blanket Mountain: Barradale's Upper Logging Camp, undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Blanket Mountain: Blanket Mountain CCC Side Camp 1458, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Blanket Mountain: Jake's Creek, undated (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Blanket Mountain: Jake's Creek Community, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Blanket Mountain: Dave Ownby Mill, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Blanket Mountain: Champion Fibre Co. Flume/Rough Creek, 1918-2000 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Blanket Mountain: Ben N. Parton Lookout, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Blanket Mountain: Lem Ownby, 1974-2003 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Blanket Mountain: Levi Trentham, 1936-2004 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Blanket Mountain: Fish Camp, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Blanket Mountain: Peawood Hollow Logging Camp, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Blanket Mountain: Higdon Camp on Three Forks Below Clingman's Dome, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Blanket Mountain: Camp 18, 1978-2005 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Blanket Mountain: Wilson Falls, 1972-2005 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Meigs Post: Meigs Post (6198'), 1914-2005 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Meigs Post: Elkmont or Wonderland Cemetery, 1920-1987 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Meigs Post: Levi Trentham Cemetery, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Meigs Post: Little Greenbriar or Walker Cemetery, 1987-1991; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 60, Folder 8] (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Meigs Post: Sallie Moore Cemetery, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Meigs Post: Lone Grave, Son of Levi Trentham, 1988-1996 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Meigs Post: Meigs Mountain Cemetery, 1978-1991 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Meigs Post: Beech Tree Cemetery or Meigs Creek Cemetery, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Meigs Post: G. L. McCarter Cemetery, undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Meigs Post: The Sink Spring Indian Cemetery, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Meigs Post: Sugarland Mountain Spring Indian Cemetery, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Meigs Post: Husky Gap Indian Cemetery, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Meigs Post: Mids Branch Cemetery, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Meigs Post: John N. Walker Cemetery, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Meigs Post: Turner Cemetery, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Meigs Post: Jake's Creek Logging Camp Cemetery, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Fighting Creek: Fighting Creek, 1925-1999 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Fighting Creek: John Ownby Cabin, 1998-2004 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Fighting Creek: Hickory Flats, undated (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Fighting Creek: Laurel Falls, 1958 August (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Fighting Creek: Bill Stinnett Mill, undated (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Fighting Creek: Glen Alpine, 1984-1997 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Fighting Creek: General Frank Maloney, 1952-1986 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Forks of the River: Fort Harry, 2001-2004; (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Forks of the River: Fort Harry, 2001-2004; (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Forks of the River: Forks of the River, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Forks of the River: Evans Chapel No. 1 Missionary Baptist Church, 1933-1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Forks of the River: Reverend Ricard Evans, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Forks of the River: Fighting Creek School, 1912-1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Forks of the River: Fighting Creek School, 1933, 1984-1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Forks of the River: Trentville, 1986-1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Forks of the River: Caleb L. Trentham Mill, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Forks of the River: Noah Trentham Tub Mill, 1984-1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Forks of the River: Ephraim Ogle Tub Mill, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Sugarlands: Sugarlands, 1975-1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Sugarlands: Campbell Overlook, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Sugarlands: Indian Gap Hotel, 1927-1931, 1983-1989 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Sugarlands: Chimneys, 1959, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Sugarlands: Grassy Patch, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Sugarlands: Uncle Joe Quilliams, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Sugarlands: Trentham, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Sugarlands: Sugarlands Baptist Church, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Sugarlands: Bridge School, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Sugarlands: Brackins School, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Sugarlands: Sugarlands Missionary Baptist Church (est. 1844), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Sugarlands: Sugarlands School, 1918-1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Sugarlands: McCarter's Chapel/United Brethren Church, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Sugarlands: Ernest and Lucinda Ogle Stone, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Sugarlands: Sam King Store, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Sugarlands: Burton Ogle Mill, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Sugarlands: Sugarlands Branch, 1983-1991 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Sugarlands: Huskey Gap School, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Sugarlands: John B. Whaley Tub Mill, 1865, 1984-1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Sugarlands: Joel Whaley's Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Sugarlands: David Bracken's Tub Mill, circa 1931 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Sugarlands: Paul Ogle Tub Mill, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Sugarlands: Uncle Joe Bradley, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Sugarlands: Lydia Kear Whaley, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Sugarlands: CCC Camp H. A. Morgan 1458, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Sugarlands: CCC Camp 1459, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Sugarlands: Sugarville, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Sugarlands: I. N. Trentham Cemetery, 1863-1865, 1984-1999 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Sugarlands: Vance Newman (also Cole) Cemetery, 1987-1993 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Sugarlands: Burton Ogle (also Sugarlands) Cemetery, 1975-1998 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Sugarlands: N. S. McCarter Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Sugarlands: Baskins Creek Cemetery, 1987-1996 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Sugarlands: Indian Grave Flats, 1956-2000 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Sugarlands: Pete Prince Archaeological Resources Protection Act (ARPA) Violation, 1931-1991; (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Sugarlands: Pete Prince Archaeological Resources Protection Act (ARPA) Violation, 1931-1991; (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Sugarlands: Pete Prince Archaeological Resources Protection Act (ARPA) Violation, 1991, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Sugarlands: The Reverend Sam Oakley Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Sugarlands: Carr Branch Cemetery, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Sugarlands: Jasper Mellinger Cemetery, 1934-1990 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Sugarlands: Unknown Cherokee Confederate Soldier Grave, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Sugarlands: Carr Branch Cemetery, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Sugarlands: Ash Hopper Branch Cemetery, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Sugarlands: Ash Hopper Gap Cemetery, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Sugarlands: Carr Gap Indian Cemetery, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Sugarlands: Bullhead Cherokee Confederate Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Sugarlands: Isaac Husky Cemetery, 1863, 1978-1990 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Sugarlands: Joel Kear Sr. Cemetery, 1871-1990 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Sugarlands: Noah Bud Ogle Cemetery, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Sugarlands: Davis Brackin Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Sugarlands: Mt. Harrison Gap Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Sugarlands: Cataract Falls Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Sugarlands: Isaac Bradley Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Sugarlands: John Kear Cemetery, 1972-1991 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Sugarlands: John B. Whaley Cemetery, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Sugarlands: Lewallen Ogle Cemetery, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Sugarlands: Little Ephraim Reagan Cemetery, 1978, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Sugarlands: Joel Whaley Cemetery, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Sugarlands: Leonard Henderson Oakley Cemetery, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Sugarlands: Steve Husky Cemetery, 1879, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Sugarlands: Mansfield Ramsey Cemetery, undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Sugarlands: Rem Ownby Cemetery, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Sugarlands: Broomtying Richard Ogle Cemetery, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Sugarlands: Henry Oakley Cemetery, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Sugarlands: Louis E. Voorheis Cemetery, 1960-2003 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Sugarlands: Reverend Henry Baker Kear Cemetery, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Sugarlands: Ashes Interred in the Great Smoky Mountains, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Gatlinburg: Gatlinburg, 1887-2005 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Gatlinburg: Battle of Gatlinburg (Civil War), 1937 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Gatlinburg: Gatlinburg, 1978-1987 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Gatlinburg: Tunnel (Newfound Gap Road), 1934 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Gatlinburg: Mountain View Hotel, 1983-1999 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Gatlinburg: John Gatlin, 1937-1997 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Gatlinburg: Pi Beta Phi School, 1920-1996; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 58, Folder 10] (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Gatlinburg: White Oak Flats, undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Gatlinburg: White Oak Flats Cemetery, 1861, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Gatlinburg: Holston Assembly Grounds, 1917-1991 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Gatlinburg: Campbell Lead, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Gatlinburg: Tom and Sophie Campbell, 1937-1986 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Gatlinburg: Mount Harrison (3520'), undated (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Gatlinburg: Robert Conner, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Gatlinburg: Harkless Whaley, undated (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Gatlinburg: The Ogle Family, 1987-2004 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Gatlinburg: Gatlinburg Post Office, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Mill Creek: Cherokee Orchard, 1937-1991; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 60, Folder 9] (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Mill Creek: Irwin Creek, 1983-2003 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Mill Creek: Alex Cole's Log Cabin, 1953-1999 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Mill Creek: Bull Head (for Cherokee Chief Uskwalena), 1928 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Mill Creek: Mill Creek, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Mill Creek: Mill Creek School, 1984-1991 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Mill Creek: Mill Creek Missionary Baptist Church, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Mill Creek: Beech Cathedral, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Mill Creek: Noah W. Bud Ogle Place, 1936-2004 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Mill Creek: Wiley M. Oakley, 1937-1984 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Mill Creek: Oscar Watson, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Mill Creek: Reverend Dan Jones Trail, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Mill Creek: Connor's Gap, undated (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Mill Creek: Rainbow Falls (83') on LeConte Creek, 1940-1958 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Mill Creek: Indian Bill, undated (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Mill Creek: Mills on Mill Creek, 1936-1991 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Mill Creek: Reagan Mill, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Mill Creek: Jim Ogle Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Mill Creek: Reverend Henry B. Kear Tub Mill, 1872-1912, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Mill Creek: Little Ephraim Reagan Tub Mill, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Mill Creek: Richard Isaiah Trentham Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Mill Creek: Nick Husky Tub Mill, 1906-1918, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Mill Creek: Caleb Ogle Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Mill Creek: Leonard Henderson Oakley Pounding Mill, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Mill Creek: Leonard Henderson Oakley Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Mill Creek: Steve Husky Tub Mill, 1879-1991 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Mill Creek: Henry C. Oakley Overshot Mill, 1879-1991 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Mill Creek: Joseph Harrison Ogle Tub Mill, 1887, 1984-1991 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Mill Creek: Harvey H. Oakley Tub Mill, 1928, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Mill Creek: Voorhie Turbine, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Mill Creek: Voorhies Overshot Mill, 1928-1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Mill Creek: Reverend Joseph Samuel Oakley Tub Mill, 1907, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Mill Creek: Noah Bud Ogle Tub Mill, 1937-1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Mill Creek: Birdwell Husky Tub Mill, 1919-1922, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Mill Creek: John H. Bullhead Husky Tub Mill No. 1, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Mill Creek: John H. Bullhead Husky Tub Mill No. 2, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Mill Creek: (Rorky) Steve Husky Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Mill Creek: Bullhead Richard Ogle Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Mill Creek: Isaac Lewallen Bud Ogle Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Mill Creek: Lucinda Oakley Ogle/Earl Ogle Pounding Mill, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Mill Creek: Anakeesta Ridge/Knob, 1932-1935, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Mill Creek: Steve Cole, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Mill Creek: Indian Grave Flats, 1991-2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Mill Creek: Indian Gap Road/Thomas Road, 1937-1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Mill Creek: Carlos C. Campbell, 1976, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Mill Creek: Grassy Patch (3840'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Mill Creek: Indian Gap (5270'), 1914-2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Mill Creek: Road Gap (now Indian Gap), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Mill Creek: Indian Beckons Carson Brewer's KNS 1962 Hikes, Bill Dyers's Cartoon, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Mill Creek: Fort Harry (article), undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Mill Creek: Huggins Hell (near Alum Cave), 1981-2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Mill Creek: Ben A. Morton Sr., 1956-2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Mill Creek: Mount Mingus (5802'), 1874-2001; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 60, Folder 10] (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Mill Creek: Duck Hawk, 1932, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Mill Creek: Evans Chapel No. 1 Cemetery, 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Mill Creek: Fighting Creek Cemetery, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Mill Creek: Stinnett Cemetery, 1987-2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Mill Creek: Ruth M. Hunter Grave, Stinnett Cemetery, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Mill Creek: Ruth M. Hunter Grave, Stinnett Cemetery, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Mill Creek: Jim Kear Mill, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Mill Creek: John Kear Tub Mill, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Mill Creek: Fort Harry Falls, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Mill Creek: Alum Cave (4917'), 1914-2000 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Mount LeConte: Woodmanston Plantation (Riceboro, Ga.), 1996-2005 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Mount LeConte: Dr. Joseph LeConte, 1858, 1934-2004 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Mount LeConte: Mount LeConte (6593'), 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Mount LeConte: Paul J. Adams, 1924-1999 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Mount LeConte: Cliff Top (6344'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Mount LeConte: LeConte Lodge, 1937-2000 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Mount LeConte: Mount Curtis (6344'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Mount LeConte: Myrtle Point (6500'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Mount LeConte: Mount Safford (6500'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Mount LeConte: Cross Knob (5931'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Mount LeConte: Neighbor (5771'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Mount LeConte: Balsam Point (5818'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Mount LeConte: Master Knob (5818'), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Mount LeConte: Mount LeConte CCC Side Camp 1458, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Mount LeConte: Balsam Potatoes (Wiley Oakley Tale), 1937 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Baskins Creek: Baskins Creek, 1933-1977 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Baskins Creek: Baskins School, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Roaring Fork: Bales Cemetery, 1939-1991 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Roaring Fork: Governor Senter Rhode Island Locomotive, 1936-2004 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Roaring Fork: Governor DeWitt Senter of Morristown, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Roaring Fork: Levi Hamilton Ogle, 1862-1907, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Roaring Fork: Gilbert Ogle, 1862, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Roaring Fork: Roaring Fork, 1928-2004 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Roaring Fork: Spruce Flats Community, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Roaring Fork: Roaring Fork Log School, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Roaring Fork: Roaring Fork Frame School, 1928-1991 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Roaring Fork: Roaring Fork Missionary Baptist Church, 1926-1985 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Roaring: Fork: Roaring Fork Primitive Baptist Church, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Roaring Fork: Laurel Grove School, undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Roaring Fork: Lawson A. Ogle Tub Mill, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Roaring Fork: Aaron Reagan Tub Mill, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Roaring Fork: Alfred Reagan Tub Mill, 1975-1983 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Roaring Fork: James Bales Tub Mill, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Roaring Fork: The Place of a Thousand Drips, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Roaring Fork: Grotto Falls, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Roaring Fork: Dome Falls, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Roaring Fork: High Falls, 1929 June 16 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Roaring Fork: Sherman Clabo Place (Last House on Roaring Fork), 1937, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Roaring Fork: Trillium Gap, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Roaring Fork: Mount Winnesoka (4308'), 1934-2000 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Roaring Fork: Molly McCarter Ogle, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Roaring Fork: Ephraim Bales (1869-1926) Cabin, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Banner: Banner, 1983-2000 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Banner: Banner School, 1926, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Banner: Banner Missionary Baptist Church (est. 1892), 1985-1993 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Banner: Cardwell Methodist Episcopal Church, 1986-1995 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Banner: Caldwell Chapel Methodist Church, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Foothills Parkway: Perry Mill, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Foothills Parkway: Gatlinburg Spur, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Foothills Parkway: General, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Pigeon Forge: Caldwell Methodist Episcopal Church, 1991 October 2 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - McCookville: McCookville, 1929, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - McCookville: McCookville School, 1912-1993 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - McCookville: Gum Stand Missionary Baptist Church, undated (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - McCookville: The Reverend Dr. Henry McCook, 1911-1913, 1994-2004; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 60, Folder 11] (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - McCookville: Fighting McCooks of Ohio, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - McCookville: Smoky Mountain Railroad, 1926-2004 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - McCookville: Knoxville, Sevierville, and Eastern Railway, 1920-1926 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - McCookville: Pigeon River Railroad, 1917-1932, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - McCookville: George Lamon (beekeeper), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - McCookville: Pigeon Forge, Tenn., undated (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - McCookville: Frazier Cemetery, 1916, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - McCookville: S. S. Dock Green Cemetery, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - McCookville: Lindsaytown Cemetery, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - McCookville: Maddron Cemetery, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - McCookville: Marion Green Cemetery, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - McCookville: Rector Cemetery, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - McCookville: Mullins Cemetery, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - McCookville: Sizemore Cemetery, 1975-1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - McCookville: John Palmer Price Cemetery, 1885, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - McCookville: Chris Parton Cemetery, 1987-2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - McCookville: Alonzo Husky Cemetery, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - McCookville: F. E. Husky Cemetery, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - McCookville: Elijah Whaley Cemetery, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - McCookville: Friendship Baptist Church Cemetery, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - McCookville: Plemons Cemetery, 1984-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - McCookville: [Dodgen-]Rayfield Cemetery, 1986-1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - McCookville: Ownby Cemetery of Long Branch, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - McCookville: Ephraim McCarter Cemetery, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - McCookville: Lone Grave, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - McCookville: Dudley Creek Cemetery, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - McCookville: Lone Grave, Nations Cemetery, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - McCookville: Pinnacle Cemetery, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - McCookville: Johnnie Ramsey Cemetery, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - McCookville: Carroll Ramsey Cemetery, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - McCookville: Snag Mountain Cemetery, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - McCookville: Injun Creek Cemetery, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - McCookville: Rayfield Cemetery, 1936, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - McCookville: Andy Huff Place Cemetery, 1982-1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - McCookville: Cowflat Branch Cemetery, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - McCookville: Baby Ownby Grave, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - McCookville: Jim Parton Cemetery, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - McCookville: Catstairs Cemetery, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - McCookville: Webb Creek Cemetery, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - McCookville: Upper Emerts Cove Cemetery, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - McCookville: Parton Hollow Indian Cemetery, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 28)